=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 3=
= طبيبي الخيالي = = الحلقة 3 =
The two people connected by the red string
الشخصان متصلان بالخيط الأحمر
will form a barrier within one foot of each other.
سيشكل حاجزًا داخل قدم واحدة من بعضها البعض.
We will be bounced back
سوف نرتد مرة أخرى
if we are out of range.
إذا كنا خارج النطاق.
(How am I going to see Nianzhou tomorrow)
(كيف سأرى نيانتشو غدا)
(if I'm stuck with him?)
(إذا علقت معه؟)
Tang.
تانغ.
Come out!
يظهر!
You quack.
أنت دجال.
Show yourself.
اظهر نفسك.
Mr. Zhang.
السيد تشانغ.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Dr. Tang.
دكتور.  كماشة.
I've eaten a ton of pig's heart.
لقد أكلت الكثير من قلب الخنزير.
My burps and farts
تجشؤي وفرتس
even smell like it.
حتى رائحة مثل ذلك.
Still, at night,
لا يزال ، في الليل ،
I have nightmares
لدي كوابيس
and sweat a lot.
والعرق كثيرا.
My wife agrees that there is
توافق زوجتي على وجود
something wrong with me.
هناك خطب بي.
I've been treated
لقد عولجت
by you for so long.
بواسطتك لفترة طويلة.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What exactly is my illness?
ما هو مرضي بالضبط؟
Mr. Zhang.
السيد تشانغ.
There are many
هنالك الكثير
different kinds of illnesses.
أنواع مختلفة من الأمراض.
Not all of them can be cured.
لا يمكن علاج كل منهم.
The medical saint, Zhang Zhongjing, once said
قال القديس الطبي تشانغ تشونغ جينغ ذات مرة
the pulse and symptoms
النبض والأعراض
will tell about your health.
سيخبرنا عن صحتك.
Treating the symptoms accordingly
معالجة الأعراض وفقًا لذلك
is a way of identifying them.
هي وسيلة للتعرف عليهم.
What's more, you have weak kidneys.
علاوة على ذلك ، لديك كلى ضعيفة.
It's a chronic disease
إنه مرض مزمن
that requires a long course of treatment.
الذي يتطلب دورة طويلة من العلاج.
You have to be patient.
عليك ان تكون صبور.
Who said I have weak kidneys?
من قال عندي ضعف في الكلى؟
My kidneys are fine!
كليتي بخير!
Tang.
تانغ.
Listen!
استمع!
I'm not easy to fool!
ليس من السهل أن أخدع!
Mr. Zhang, what...
السيد تشانغ ، ماذا ...
Give me my money back.
أعد إلي نقودي.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I will
أنا سوف
smash this place up!
حطم هذا المكان!
Stagnation of Qi
ركود تشي
and blood stasis.
وركود الدم.
Emotional disturbances
الاضطرابات العاطفية
can develop a negative impact on the liver.
يمكن أن تتطور إلى تأثير سلبي على الكبد.
Who exactly are you?
من انت بالضبط
Who will believe you?
من سيصدقك؟
You often have
غالبًا ما يكون لديك
symptoms of weak erection
أعراض ضعف الانتصاب
during intercourse.
أثناء الجماع.
I have a remedy
لدي علاج
to keep your sexual life
للحفاظ على حياتك الجنسية
and kidneys healthy.
والكلى صحية.
What remedy?
ما العلاج؟
Follow this prescription
اتبع هذه الوصفة
and get three sets of medicine.
وتحصل على ثلاث مجموعات من الأدوية.
If you still don't see any results,
إذا كنت لا تزال لا ترى أي نتائج ،
you come here again
تعال إلى هنا مرة أخرى
and name the price of compensation.
وتسمية ثمن التعويض.
Go and get the herbs.
اذهب واحصل على الأعشاب.
Fine.
بخير.
You said so yourself.
قلت ذلك بنفسك.
I didn't blackmail you.
أنا لم ابتزك.
Yes.
نعم.
He can name the price?
يمكنه تسمية السعر؟
What if he asks for more?
ماذا لو طلب المزيد؟
It is the physician's duty
إنه واجب الطبيب
to heal and save lives.
للشفاء وإنقاذ الأرواح.
If you don't have that kind of confidence,
إذا لم يكن لديك هذا النوع من الثقة ،
you're not qualified to be a physician.
أنت غير مؤهل لأن تكون طبيباً.
Are you really a physician?
هل انت حقا طبيب؟
I'm the Divine Physician.
أنا الطبيب الإلهي.
Fine.
بخير.
Divine Physician.
طبيب إلهي.
Can you write the prescription again
هل يمكنك كتابة الوصفة مرة أخرى
for me?
لي؟
I'll take a picture and send it to my father.
سألتقط صورة وأرسلها إلى والدي.
I don't want to make any more trouble.
لا أريد أن أجعل المزيد من المتاعب.
You should say,
يجب عليك القول،
"Divine Physician,
"الطبيب الإلهي ،
could you please teach me the prescription you made earlier?"
هل يمكنك أن تعلمني الوصفة الطبية التي قدمتها سابقًا؟ "
You're not qualified to
أنت غير مؤهل
study medicine from me.
دراسة الطب مني.
Chinese medicine is all about herb-herb interaction.
يدور الطب الصيني حول التفاعل بين الأعشاب والأعشاب.
One herb may alter the effect of the other.
عشب واحد قد يغير تأثير الآخر.
It should not be used indiscriminately.
لا ينبغي استخدامه بشكل عشوائي.
You prescribed him pig's heart
لقد وصفت له قلب الخنزير
without any other medicine.
بدون أي دواء آخر.
No wonder the effect is slow.
لا عجب أن يكون التأثير بطيئًا.
There's no harm anyway.
لا يوجد ضرر على أي حال.
Suit yourself.
تتناسب معك.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض